Guide to the Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Housing TAM.606
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Housing Web Archive
2012-
TAM.606
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
0.0010 linear feet (1+ websites; i.e., a collection of websites that grows on an ongoing basis)
This collection contains the archived websites of housing rights, movements, and policy organizations, with a special concentration on New York City. Issues include, affordable housing, rent control, public housing, housing law and legislation.
Tamiment Library.
Historical/Biographical Note
Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Housing was created with the Web Archiving Service from the California Digital Library. This service employs open source web archiving utilities developed by Internet Archive with the support of the The International Internet Preservation Consortium. The Web Archiving Service was made possible with support from the National Digital Information and Infrastructure Preservation Program and the University of California, as part of a project to preserve born-digital political communication. The role of the Tamiment Library during this project and thereafter was/is to create topically based archives of websites documenting contemporary and ongoing labor and left activity, principally that based in the United States.
Scope and Content Note
This collection contains the archived websites of housing rights, movements, and policy organizations, with a special concentration on New York City. Issues include, affordable housing, rent control, public housing, housing law and legislation. For technical, privacy and other reasons, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically.
Related Archival Materials
A list of related Tamiment Library web archives, whose ns2:titles all begin with the prefix "Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left)," can be found at the web page Web Archives from New York University Libraries.
Housing policy |z New York (State) |z New York.; Housing policy |z United States.; Housing |x Law and legislation |z New York (State) |z New York.; Housing |x Law and legislation |z United States.; Housing |z New York (State) |z New York.; Housing |z United States.; Landlord and tenant |z New York (State) |z New York.; Tenants' associations |z New York (State) |z New York.
- Housing
  - Amalgamated Housing Cooperative, 3/28/2012-
  - Association for Neighborhood and Housing Development, 3/17/2012-
  - Brighton Beach Neighborhood Association, 3/10/2012-
  - Cooper Square Committee, 3/10/2012-
  - Cooperative Village, 3/28/2012-
  - Cypress Hills Local Development Corporation, 3/07/2012-
  - Foreclosure Fraud, 3/6/2012-
  - Good Old Lower East Side, 3/07/2012-
  - Housing Conservation Coordinators, 3/11/2012-
  - Housing is a Human Right, 3/4/2012-
  - Independence Plaza North Tenant Association, 3/10/2012-
  - Make the Road New York, 3/10/2012-
  - Margert Community Corporation, 3/16/2012-
  - Metropolitan Council on Housing, 3/4/2012-
  - National Coalition for the Homeless, 3/27/2012-
  - National Housing Law Project, 3/5/2012-
  - National Low Income Housing Coalition, 3/5/2012-
  - Neighbors Helping Neighbors, 3/06/2012
  - New York State Tenant and Neighbors Coalition, 3/07/2012-
  - Northern Manhattan Improvement Corporation, 3/04/2012-
  - Northwest Bronx Community and Clergy Coalition, 3/6/2012-
  - Park West Village Tenants' Association, 3/13/2012-
  - Penn South, 3/26/2012-
  - Pratt Area Community Council, 3/2/2012-
  - RiverBay Corporation, 3/28/2012-
  - Shalom Tenants Alliance, 3/05/2012-
  - St. Nicholas Neighborhood Preservation Corporation, 3/04/2012-
  - Stuyvesant Town-Peter Cooper Village Tenants Association, 3/15/2012-
  - Tenants Political Action Committee, 3/02/2012-
  - United Neighborhood Houses of New York, 3/17/2012-